[{"answer": "I want to know this.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 12, "question": "David Frost?", "qSentId": 11}, {"answer": "Nice to be with you.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "It wouldn't be better.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Or better?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "I think being the front-runner is tough.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Is it easier coming when you're not a favorite?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Maybe.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Isn't it worth paying more money?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "My view of Sarah Palin is she is the most dynamic figure maybe in politics, even more in some ways than President Obama, who is a little more scripted than she is.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "What is your view of Sarah Palin?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Except for the use of the word, absolutely right on.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Is she right?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Blood libel.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Which word?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Because you know what the media is going to do.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Why do you do that unless it's inherently, you think it's wrong?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Not if I had thought about it.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Would you have ever done -- I don't know if you ever did -- but what you have ever done a website of your own which had crosshairs aimed at political targets?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Of course it would.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Given the furor, though, do you think it would now be prudent for politicians to not do that?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "You know, it depends.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "Is Sarah Palin too polarizing to win against Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "It depends on the job he does.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "But against President Obama?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Maybe the opposite.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Would you be more tempted to run if she wasn't?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Maybe the opposite because my one chance, if I have a chance, is that I'm considered a moderate Republican.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "I find some of the outpourings of all of these movements bordering on extremist.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Do you agree on some of the outpourings of the Tea Party bordering on bigotry?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Isn't that bad for American society?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "So isn't there a real inherent danger?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Why are you creating two parties?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "If I were him, I would be saying the State of the Union is strong, which I do think it is.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "If you were him, what would you be saying?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "First of all he should be saying it's strong.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "What should he be saying?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Is it eight?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Would you raise taxes?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Can you honestly say that?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "We collect taxes.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "But is it as simple as that, really?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I did not.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Did you know Bernie Madoff?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "When you were mayor, you had no inkling of what he was up to?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "It hasn't come to the result we want yet.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Rudy, the war in Afghanistan isn't working, is it?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "I think there could be, yes.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "If I invite you back in 2015, do you honestly think that there will be any kind of tangible victory in Afghanistan?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Probably all three.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Or Iraq?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "I think it would be a mistake right now to invade Iran.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Using the same yardstick of argument that you used with Saddam Hussein?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "North Korea is a different situation which we can talk about different things involving North Korea.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "And I'm assuming North Korea presumably?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Absolutely, absolutely.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Do you believe fundamentally that America should be doing more of these trips?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "It would depend on what could be accomplished.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Would you meet with Hezbollah, with al Qaeda?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "If America has the objective of obtaining advantages from it.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "But as a principle, you believe it is probably time that America talked more to its enemies?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Would you meet this group again?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "I didn't think so.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Given that Pakistan and countries like that are clearly unstable and in possession of a number of weapons, is this really the right time for America to be downgrading?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "IULIANI: Probably less, for the simple fact that they're looking for it more.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Is America as susceptible now to another attack like that as it was then, do you think?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Very surprised.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Are you surprised, in a good way, that there hasn't been another huge attack on American mainland in the last decade?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "One of the police officers that was with me came up to my counsel, Denny Young, who was having breakfast with me, and Bill Simon was the third person.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "How did you hear what had happened?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "IULIANI: I'm thinking how do I get air support for the city.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "What are you now thinking?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "I thought if I said a number like 12,000, it would -- it would just create even more fear, more shock, possibly even panic.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Why did you say that?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Being the president is very different, because there is a whole obligation.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "If you had been the president?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "My staff used to then tease me and say oh, gee, we have a little more Anthrax.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Why would you do that, Rudy?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "That's not an official position.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "How did you take that?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "No, not a day.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Is there ever a day when you don't think about 9/11?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "I was annoyed with using it as a political device.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "How did you feel when the 9/11 Health Care Bill was being debated and there were Republicans who did not want that to go through?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "thought that one transcends politics.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "-- that transcend politics?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "That we're very resilient, that we can take the worst attack in our history and we can come back from it.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "What do you think America learned about itself after 9/11?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "It was fascinating.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "What was it like being knighted by the queen of England?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "I did it two or three times as part of --", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Did you regularly dress up in women's clothes?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "No, I think I -- I had a much better career than I ever expected.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Would you have rather been a great movie star, do you think?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "It's fabulous.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "How is marriage the third time around?", "qSentId": 659}, {"answer": "You don't feel good about it, because it affects your family.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "Sure, I guess you'd wished if you had gone back, you had done it better, done it differently.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Did you have any big regrets about the impact of your political life on your family life?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "Probably the same day.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "What would you say has been the best day of your life?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "Out of an attempt to really demoralize and destabilize America, oddly unity and strength came out of that?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "Yeah, I will.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "Would you come back nearer the time of the anniversary?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "Yes, I've always believed, Piers, the scripture shows that it's a sin.", "docId": "110124pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "Is homosexuality a sin in your eyes?", "qSentId": 733}]